제작 - 네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
1x01 The '70s Pilot
Aug 23, 1998 on FOX
위스콘신주 포인트 플레이스
1976년 5월 17일
오후 8:47
장소:
에릭 포먼네 지하실
에릭, 지금이 기회야
Eric, it is time!
니가 하지 그러냐?
Why don't you do it?
- 너희 집이잖아
- 너희 집
- It's your house.
- Your house.
위에서 나는 소릴 들어봐
Listen to them up there.
파티가 한창이라고
The party has reached
critical mass.
10분 뒤면 맥주 가져올
기회는 사라질거야
In 10 minutes, there will be
no more beer opportunities.
내가 맥주에 손대는 걸
아빠가 알면 날 죽일거야
If my dad catches me
copping beers, he'll kill me.
니가 죽는 위험은 내 감수하지
I'm willing to take that risk.
걱정하지 말고, 조용히 움직여
Don't worry about it.
Just remain calm, keep moving.
무엇보다도
우리 아빠 머리에 현혹되지 마
And above all, don't get sucked
into my dad's hair.
너네 아빠 머리가 어떤데?
What's wrong
with your dad's hair?
그냥 보지 마
Just don't look at it...
그리고 에릭
And Eric,
시원한 걸로, 겁나 시원한 걸로
cold, definitely cold.
♪ 젊고 아름다운 그대의 외모는
언젠가 사라질지니 ♪
♪ Young and beautiful,
someday your looks will be gone... ♪
오, 오, 에릭, 조심해라
피자롤이 뜨겁다
Oh, oh, Watch it Eric,
hot pizza rolls.
비켜주세요
뜨거워요! 뜨거워!
Coming throught, hot hot!
키티, 어디 계세요?
Kitty, where are you?
네, 두개 드셔도 돼요
아주 많이 준비했어요
Okay, take two, there's plenty,
there's plenty coming!
모두들 어떠세요?
Is everybody good?
네, 알아요
비엔나소세지는 다목적이죠
I know, I know, vienna saussages
are so versatile!
잘 있었니? 에릭
Hi there, Eric!
핀씨오티씨!
Mr. Pinciotti!
그래, 에릭, 아저씨 새 헤어스타일
어떠니? 섹시하지 않니?
So, Eric, how do yo like
Bob's new hair? Isn't it groovy?
정말 죽이는데요, 핀씨오티 아줌마!
It's incredibly groovy,
Mrs. Pinciotti!
오 그래, 이 사람 아이디어였단다
Oh yeah, it was Midge's idea.
파마한 거란다
It's a perm.
에릭?
Eric?
네, 아버지
Hi, dad!
밥 머리는 대체 어떻게 된거냐?
What the hell happened
to Bob's hair?
그러게요
Beats me!
꼭 푸들 엉덩이 같구만
His head looks like a poodle's ass!
세상 더 볼 게 없다고 생각했었는데...
Boy, just when you think
you've seen everything...
푸들 엉덩이가 파티에 왔죠
A poodle's ass walks
into your party!
에릭, 'ass'란 말 쓰지마라
너 아직 고등학생이야
Eric, don't use the ass word,
you're still in high school.
네, 아버님!
Yes, Sir.
*담요에 만 돼지고기에요, 뜨거워요!
pigs in a blanket: 쏘세지롤
Okay, pigs in a blanket!
Hot hot!
키티, 도로에 있는 토요타
자동차가 당신네 건가요?
Kitty, is that your Toyota in the drive?
레드, 토요타라고?
Red, a Toyota?
그래, 내 꺼야
Yeah, it's mine!
마지막으로 일제기계가 이렇게
가깝게 있었을 땐
I tell you, the last time I was that
close to a japanese machine,
그게 날 쏘고 있었지!
it was shooting at me.
여보, 석유 파동이라는데
어쩌겠어요?
Well honey, it is the gas crisis,
what can you do?
게다가, 그 대리점에 있는 개자식들이
And you know Bob, those SOBs
at the dealership offered me
내 비스타크루저를 겨우
400 달러 쳐주겠다더군
a lousy 400 dollar trade-in
on the Vista Cruiser!
그럼, 어쩔건데?
Yeah, what you gonna do?
그렇게 파느니 마당에서 썩히고 말지
It' ll rust in the driveway
before I trade it in.
여보, 벌써 썩고 있는 걸요?
Honey, it is rusting in te driveway.
아빠, 그럼 그차 저 주세요
Hey pa, I'll take the Cruiser
off your hands.
기름 잡아먹는 기계라도 상관없어요
I don't care if it's a pump-sucker.
너 들고 있는게 뭐냐, 에릭?
What you got there Eric?
맥주요
Beer!
앉아있다가, 발견했는데
I found it, just sitting,
저...
you know,
그냥 옆에 있길래
around.
음, 그럼 치워라, 아들아
Well, put them away, son!
네, 그러려고요
Why, I intend to, sir!
오, 얘야, 얘야
Oh, honey, honey,
지하실에 가는 길에
이것들 좀 냉장고에 넣어주겠니?
on your way to the basement,
could you pop these in the fridge?
미지근해졌지 뭐니?
They're warm!
♪ 'Jackie Blue'
by Ozark Mountain Daredevils ♪
이것 좀 봐
Check it out.
난 그거 맨날 보는데
I see that everyday.
에릭이 살아 있었어!
He's alive!
좋은 소식이 있어
Good news.
우리 아빠가 비스타크루저를
나에게 줄까 생각중이셔
My dad is thinking of giving me...
the VistaCruiser.
너 차 갖게 되는 거야?
You're getting a car?
오, 내가 에릭 너 정말
끝내준다고 말했던가?
Ooh! Have I told you how
incredibly attractive you are, Eric?
아니
No.
나한테 에릭 귀엽다고 했잖아
You told me he was cute!
그런 말 한 적 없어
No, I didn't!
에릭한테는 아무 말도
말라고 까지 해서 기억한단 말야
I remember, 'cause you said
not to say anything in front of Eric.
얘들아, 중요한 일에 집중하자
Let's focus on
what's important here, people!
포먼이 도둑질을 해냈어
포먼을 위하여!
Forman stole something!
To Forman!
포먼을 위하여!
슬픈게 뭔 줄 알아?
You know what's sad?
오늘이 내 생애에서
가장 자랑스러운 날이라는 거지
This is the proudest day of my life!
토퍼 그레이스 (에릭 포먼)
밀라 커니스 (재키 벅하트)
애쉬튼 커쳐 (마이클 켈소)
대니 메스털슨 (스티븐 하이드)
로라 프레폰 (도나 핀씨오티)
윌머 발더라마 (페즈)
데브라 조 러프 (키티 포먼)
커트우드 스미스 (레드 포먼)
타냐 로버츠 (미지 핀씨오티)
돈 스탁 (밥 핀씨오티)
That '70s Show 자막팀
싱크, 번역 : 김은경(toy69@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
That '70s Show 자막팀
싱크 : 김은경(toy69@nate)
싱크수정 : 김현정(fuchs@nate)
마샤, 축구공에 얼굴을 맞다니
아프겠다!
Well Marcia, a football in the face,
that's gotta hurt!
아야, 내코!
Ouch, my nose!
아침에는 부어오르겠는걸
That's gonna be huge
in the morning!
내 가슴보다 크게?
Huger than my boobs?
음, 왼쪽 가슴보다는 크게
Well, bigger than the left one!
우리 왜 소리도 없이 보는건데?
Why are we watching this
without the sound?
하나도 모르겠잖아
I am totally confused.
자, 이어폰을 써
Here, use the earphone.
그래서
So,
비스타크루저는 어떻게 됐어?
what's the deal
with the Vista Cruiser?
아직 아무 일도 없어
The deal is, there is no deal yet!
쉬!
SHH!
우리 콘서트에 어떻게 가지?
How are we gonna
get to the concert?
조용히 해
Shut-up!
무슨 콘서트?
What concert?
어...토드 런그렌
Uh...Todd Rundgren.
언제?
When?
이번 주말에
This weekend.
오, 누가 가는데?
Oh...Who's going?
어.. 에릭이랑 도나랑 나랑
하이드랑 외국학생 페즈랑...
Uh... Eric and Donna and me
and Hyde and the foreign kid Fez...
거의 다 지
pretty much everybody...
그리고 너도?
And you!
오, 좋아, 좋아, 좋아!
Oh, good, good good good!
나한테도 말해줘서
무지 고맙구나, 마이클
Thank you for telling me, Michael!
난 음료수 좀 마시러 갈래
Okay, well, I'm getting a soda!
- 나도!
- 앉아 있어
- Yup, me, too!
- Sit down!
너 내가 콘서트에 가는 게
싫은 거지? 그렇지?
You don't want me to go
to the concert! Is that it?
네가 음악을 좋아할 지 몰라서...
I didn't know if you liked ... music!
마이클
Michael!
난 네가 내 친구들을
좋아하지 않길래
I didn't invite you to the concert
콘서트에 같이 가자고 안한거야
because I know you
really don't like my friends!
쟤네들한테 그렇게 말했어?
Did you tell them that?
아니
No.
마이클!
Michael!
우리끼리 한 얘기를
다른 사람에게 하지마, 마이클
Don't tell our private conversations
to other people, Michael!
우리만의 비밀도 있어야지
We have to have our own
private conversations!
게다가, 난 네가 '토드 런그렌'을
좋아하는지 몰랐어
Also, I didn't think you'de be
interested in Todd Rundgren.
너 좋아하는 피터 프럼프턴도 아니잖아
Peter Frampton: 영국 출신 인기 가수
I mean, like you said,
he's no Frampton.
나도 '토드 런더먼' 좋아해
'토드 런그렌'을 잘못알고 있음
I love Todd Runddamen.
'Hello it's me!'
싱글 앨범도 있단 말야
I have the 45 of 'Hello it's me!'
우리가 같이 들었던 밤 기억나?
Remember the night
we listened to it?
콘서트에가면
재밌게 보낼 수 있는데
We can have fun at the concert, too.
특히 돌아오는 차안에서
Especially in the car
on the way back.
좋아, 너도 가자
Okay, you can go!
네가 가기를 원한다면
Only if you want me to!
오, 물론 원하지
Oh, I want you to!
재키
Jackie!
너도 우리랑 같이
콘서트에 가는 것 같구나
I guess you're going
to the concert with us.
그래, 무척 기대돼
Uhuh. I can't wait.
마이클
So Michael,
우리집에 가서
'토드 그러뇽' 레코드 들을래?
you wanna go back to my house
and listen to Todd Grunion records?
그래, 물론이지
Yeah, sure.
안녕
Ok, bye-bye.
재밌게 보내라, 안녕
You kids have fun! Bye!
안녕
Bye bye now!
쟤네 정말 귀엽다
Oh..they're so darn cute
사람만 안 보이면
개처럼 달려든다니까
and when you turn your back
they go at it like ducks!
Oh, they're frisky!
활발하잖아!
쟤들만 둘 수가 없잖아
Can't leave them alone!
안되지
No!
근데
You know,
우리 누나는 우리야말로
우리끼리만 있으면 안된다는데?
my sister thinks
that we shouldn't be left alone.
우리?
Us?
그러게...
Yes...
근데 지금 우리만 있네
We're alone now.
음
Well,
그래
Yeah.
에릭, 긴장풀어
Eric, relax.
우린 정말 오래 옆집에서 살았잖아
We've lived next door
to each other forever.
넌 4살 때
날 가질 수도 있었어
You could've had me
when I was four!
그랬지
Really,
근데 난 하루종일 *호피티만 탔지
hipitihop : 말모양의 고무공
and there I was all day
on the hippity hop!
멍청이 멍청이 멍청이...
Stupid stupid stupid...
멍청이
Stupid.
심했다
Duper.
어제부터, 난 네 생각 밖에 안 나
Ever since yesterday,
I can't stop thinking about you.
사실 평생 널 알아왔지만
I mean, I've known you
practically my whole life.
널 원해
I want you!
너무나 간절히 원해
I want you so bad!
에릭, 그건 차잖아
Eric, it's a car!
- 둘만 있게 해주자
- 그래
Let's just leave these two kids
alone. / Yeah.
- 안녕, 도나!
- 안녕, 아빠
- Say, Hey there, Donna!
- Hey, Dad.
아, 꼬맹이들이
마당에서 노는 걸 보니
Ah you kids, standing
around the driveway.
정말 귀엽구나
It's so darn cute!
너네들은 깨닫지 못하겠지만
You know, you may not realize it,
그때가 제일로 좋은 시절이란다
but this is the most fun
you're ever gonna have.
그럼 이제는
재미없는 일만 남았나요?
So it's all downhill from here, sir?
그렇지
Yeah!
너네 아빠 머리가 어떻게 된거니?
What happened to your dad's hair?
파마(permanent)하셨어
He got a permanent.
저러고 평생(permanent)을?
So, that's permanent?
♪ 'Space Truckin'
by Deep Purple ♪
내가 영어를 잘못해서
맞는 표현인지는 모르겠지만
I may not say this right
because I am new to english,
저 여자 가슴 빵빵한 거 맞지?
but she has
tremendous breasts, yes?
마이클, 쟤는 누구니?
Michael, who is this guy?
아, 페즈야
외국인 교환학생이지
Oh, that's Fez.
He's the foreign exchange student.
뭐랑 쟤를 교환했는데?
What do we exchange for him?
도나, 나 화장실 가야겠다
Donna, I have to go
to the ladies room.
도나
Donna!
나도 화장실 가고 싶어, 에릭?
I, too, must go to the bathroom. Eric?
아, 그거 남자들끼리는 안 써
No, it doesn't work
that way with guys.
켈소, 우리가 얼마나 더
재키 꼴을 참고 봐야 하는거야?
Kelso, how much longer are
we gonna have to deal
with the whole 'Jackie' experience?
걱정하지마
Don't worry,
끝낼거야
I'm breaking up with her.
- 그럴 리가
- 정말이야
- Never gonna happen.
- It's over.
내 자유시간을 빼앗고 있단 말야
She's cutting into my free time.
♪ 난 감정에 사로잡혔어요~ ♪
♪ I...I...I...I...I...
I'm hooked on a feeling~ ♪
♪ 난 믿고 싶어요~ ♪
♪ I'm high on believing~ ♪
아저씨는 아직도 너에게
차를 줄까말까 생각중이시니?
So is Red still thinking
about giving you the car maybe?
차가 생겨도 기름값이
장난이 아니게 들거야
Even if we do get it, we're gonna
need some serious gas money
비스타크루저는 배니까
'cause the Crusier's a boat.
나도 알아
I know it's a boat.
이 석유 파동이란 거
정말 짜증나
This whole gas shortage bites!
누가 배가 생기는데?
Who's getting a boat?
석유 파동은 없어
There is no gas shortage man!
모두 꾸며낸 거야
It's all fake.
석유회사가 모든 것을 조종한다고
The oil companies
control everything!
물로 가는 차를
발명한 사람이 있는데
Like there's this guy who invented
this car that runs on water, man!
유리섬유공냉엔진이 있어서
물로 간대
It's got fiberglass air-cooled
engine and it runs on water!
그럼 배네
So it is a boat.
아냐, 차야
No, it's a car.
단지 기름통에
기름 대신 물을 넣고
Only, you put water
in the gas tank instead of gas.
물을 연료로 해서 가는거지
And it runs on water, man!
그런 얘기 처음 들어
I never heard of this car.
야, 재키가 기름값 대면 되겠다
Hey, Jackie's good for gas money
넌 정말 남창이야
You are such a whore!
언제 배가 오는데, 남창아?
When does the boat
get here, whore?
에릭?
Eric!
네, 아빠?
Yeah dad?
얘기 좀 하자
I need to talk to you!
에릭, 네 엄마하고 얘기를 해봤는데
Eric, your mother and I
have been talking.
내가 공장에서
파트타임 근무로 강등도 됐고
Since I've been cut down
to part-time at the plant,
병원은 가까우니까
and the hospital is so close,
내가 토요타를 몰고
엄마는 버스를 타기로 했다
I can take the Toyota to work
and your mom can take the bus.
여보, 차라리 걷는 게 낫다니까요
Honey, honey really,
I'd rather walk.
간호사옷 입고 버스 타면
When I ride the bus
in my nurse's uniform,
사람들이 자기 상처들을
보여준단 말예요
people always show
me their scars.
그럼 공장에 가는 길에 태워주겠소
Then I'll drop you off
on my way to the plant.
아뇨, 아뇨, 귀찮게 하기 싫어요
No, no, I don't wanna be any trouble.
그럼 에릭이 할거야
Then Eric'll do it.
오 여보, 얘는 10대잖아요
그런 건 하고 싶지 않을...
Oh honey, he's a teenager,
he doesn't wanna drop...
엄마를 태워다 주기 싫다면
Well, if he can't drop
his own mother off at work,
절대로 차는 못 가지지
well, then, I'll be damned
if he's getting a car .
- 알았어요
- 잠깐만요
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
제게 차를 주시는 건가요?
Am I getting the car?
그런 말은 안 했다
We didn't say that.
거저 먹을 수 있는 일은 없다, 에릭
Things don't just drop
into your lap, Eric.
이 세상에서는!
Not in this life.
차는 책임감이란다
A car is a responsibility.
보험도 들어야 해
You'll need insurance.
보험료가 얼만지 알기는 아냐?
Do you have any idea
how much insurance is?
차는 애물단지란다
A car is a privilege.
오일 교환, 비상 조명탄
부동액, 모두 네가 알아서 해야 돼
Oil changes, road flares, fluids,
that's your job!
차는 바퀴달린 침실이 아니란다
A car is not a bedroom on wheels.
항상 양보해라! 항상!
Always yield! Always!
로리의 친구가 차에서 임신을 했단다
그런 일이 있어선 안 돼
Laurie's friend got pregnant in a car.
Don't let that happen.
차에서 만약 맥주깡통이 하나라도
발견되는 날엔 끝인 줄 알아라
If I find one beer can in that car,
it's over!
도너츠도 안 돼!
And no donuts either!
개미 생겨요
Ants!
그럼 제가 차를 가져도 돼요?
So, do I get the car?
좆나 좋아!
Bitching!
에릭
Eric,
엄마 앞에서 그런 말 쓰지 마라
not in front of your mother!
고마워요 아빠
Thank you, pop.
아버님
sir.
음, 그럼
Yeah, well,
다락방 청소해라
clean the attic!
켈소, 친절하기도 해라
Kelso, that's sweet!
아냐, 내가 조수석에 타려고
Actually, I'm riding shotgun.
안돼
No, you're not.
난 뒤에는 안 탈거야
Well, I'm not riding in the back.
에릭이 결정하라고 하자
Why don't we let Eric decide.
에릭?
Eric?
켈소
Kelso.
뒤에 타
Get in the back!
한 바퀴 돌아보려고?
Taking her for a spin eh?
네, 아버님!
Yes sir!
좋은 시간 보내렴
Well, have a good time.
오, 한 가지 더
차에 관해 아주 중요한 건데
Oh, one more thing,
very important, about the car.
얜 아주 낡았다
그러니까 마을 밖에 몰고 나가지마
She's old.
So no trips out of town,
절대로
ever.
알았냐?
Understood?
그럼, 잘 놀다 와라
Well, have fun!
어, 그럴 줄 알았어
우리 못 가겠다
Well, I guess that's that.
We're not going.
에릭, 가고 싶어?
Eric, do you wanna go?
마을 밖으로 가지 말라시잖아
He said no trips out of town.
이건 네 차야
가고 싶어?
It's your car. Do you wanna go?
하지만 아빤 하느님이야
But he's God!
내 생각에는 하느님도 우리가
밀워키로 가길 원하시는 것 같아
I think God would want
us to go to Milwaukee.
에릭, 넌 17살이나 먹은 남자야
Eric, you are
a seventeen year-old man.
네가 하자는 대로 할게
Gonna go with whatever you say.
네가 결정할 일이야
It's your decision.
그래, 내가 결정할 일이지
It is my decision.
내 결정은
And my decision is
콘서트에 가는 거야
we're going to a concert.
예!
Yeah!
애들이 가네요
Huh. The kids are off.
어디로 가는 걸까?
I wonder where they're going.
마을 밖
Out of town.
확실해요?
Are you sure?
물론이지
Of course,
내가 가지 말라고 했거든
I told them not to.
그럼, 한동안은 집에
아무도 없겠네요
So, I guess they'll be
gone for a while.
그렇지
Yeah.
올라가지
Let's go!
기름이 떨어진 것 같아
I'm telling you, we're out of gas.
기름 떨어진 게 아냐
We're not out of gas!
배터리가 다 됐어
It's the battery.
6년이나 돼서 맛이 갔어
It's 6 years old and shot to hell.
아무래도 아빠한테 전화해야겠다
I know what.
I'll just call my dad.
켈소, 좀 말려봐
Kelso, tell her!
에릭은 차 가지고 마을밖으로
나오면 안되는 거였어
He can't take the car out of town.
쟤네 아빠한테 전화할 거 아냐
I'm not calling his dad.
부모님들은 우리가 어떻게 사고치는지
서로 얘기하신단 말야
Jackie, parents talk to each other
about how we screw up.
왜 그런 얘길 하시는데?
Why would they talk about that?
부모님들도 어쩔 수 없는거야
They can't help it.
파티가 있다 쳐봐
Look, say there's a party, see.
그럼 부모님이 모두 함께 계시지
And all of our parents
are there. Together.
여어 레드, 우리 자식들이 친한
친구여서 잘됐지 않나?
Hi Red, say isn't it great all our
kids are such good friends?
그러게요, 재키 아빠
Yes, Jackie's dad.
젊은 애들끼리 정말
잘 몰려다닌다니까, 하하하!
They're quite the gang
of young people! Hahaha!
키티, 부엌 꾸민 게 참 맘에 들어요
Kitty, I love what you've
done with the kitchen!
네, 바다색과 노란색이죠
어쩌고 저쩌고, 조잘조잘
Yes, aqua and yellow.
Blah blah blah, yak, yak , yak.
말이 나왔으니 말인데 에릭이 자네
허락도 없이 차 가지고 밀워키 갔을 때
Speaking of kids, wasn't it lucky
triple A pulled Eric's butt out of the fire
자동차 보험회사 덕에 살았다던데
정말 다행이지 않나?
when he took the car to Milwaukee
without your permission?
뭐라고? 이 망나니 같은 놈!
10년 동안 외출금지다!
What? Why, that twisted little monkey!
I'm grounding him for ten years!
이놈들, 너희들 이제 어떻게 할래?
Kids, what are you gonnna do?
의미없는 규칙과 잔소리로
놈들을 잔뜩 고문하자구
I say we torture them with plenty
of pointless rules and advice!
여러분, 허슬 춤을 춰요!
Hey everybody, let's hustle!
얘들아, 우리는 외딴 곳에 와 있어
Okay guys, we are
in the middle of nowhere.
그리고 난 화장실에 가야겠어
And I have to go to the ladies room.
도나!
Donna!
어디들 가는데?
So, where you going?
런그렌 콘서트요
Rundgren concert.
멋진데
Cool.
그래서? 배터리 갈아 줄까?
So, what? You want a battery?
배터리 바꿔줄 수 있어
'Cause I can get you a battery.
싼가요?
Are they cheap,
어쩌면 공짜?
or possibly free?
최소 32 달러지
Thirty-two bucks, minimum.
좋아요, 이렇게 해요
Alright, I'll tell you what.
우리 배터리에다 5달러 줄테니
새 배터리로 바꿔줘요
We'll trade you our battery plus five
bucks for one of your batteries.
그것도 좋은 생각이구나
Well, that's a really
sweet deal, my friend,
근데 이럼 어떠냐, 콘서트 티켓 2장이랑
새 배터리랑 교환하는 건?
but how about this: how about
one battery for two concert tickets.
안돼요, 2장을 포기할 순 없어요
No, we can't give up two tickets.
맘대로 해
Okay.
야, 그렇게 하지 않으면 아무도 못 가
Hey, its either that or none of us go.
그럼 누가 빠지는데?
So, who's out?
우리에겐 재키가 있잖아
Well, there's always Jackie.
재키는 당근이지
그러니까 재키는 빠질거고
Of course Jackie.
I mean Jackie's gone!
또 한 명은?
But who else?
음, 글쎄... 재키 애인?
Well I don't know... Jackie's date?
야아! 재키랑 끝낼 거라니까
Come on! You know
I'm breaking up with her!
너희들이 나를 버리다니
You guys are chopping me out
재키 수다를 족히 한 시간은
들어야 했단 말야
I've had to listen to her
for a good hour.
징하게!
A really long hour!
하느님은 날 미워해
God hates me.
어떻게 하느님이 널
미워한단 말을 해?
How can you say God hates you?
넌 그래도 널 사랑하는 여자가 있잖아
At least you have a woman's love.
웃어, 남창아
Be happy, whore!
이 옷은 편하게 입는 옷이죠
This suit is for leisure.
하지만 작업할 때도 자주 입어요
But many times I wear it
to get down to business.
얘들아, 랜디의 애인이 남자야
Hey guys, Randy's date is a man
난 그런 건 괜찮아
I'm okay with it!
그게 괜찮다니 우린 정말 쿨하다니까
We're so cool to be okay with it
화장실 가야겠어
I have to go to the bathroom.
케빈!
Kevin!
나중에 설명해 줄게
I'll explain later!
안되겠어
This isn't working.
아냐, 보이 스카웃 벨트라 그래
이 벨트는 잠금...
No, it's a boyscout belt.
The buckle's got a thing you...
아니, 마이클, 내말 먼저 들어
No, Michael, before you speak
please hear my words.
우리 헤어져야 될까봐
I think we should break up.
지금?
Now?
너 재미있게 보내지도 못하잖아?
You're not having a good time.
난 재미있는데?
I'm having a good time.
- 정말?
- 그래!
- Really?
- Yeah!
오 마이클, 네가 나랑 헤어지고
싶지 않다니 정말 기뻐
Oh Michael, I am so glad
you don't wanna break up.
나랑 있으려고 티켓따위는
포기할 정도로 멋지다니
You're so nice to give your ticket
away, so you could be with me.
어, 그렇지!
Well, yeah!
그건 네가 음악, 콘서트
친구 모두 필요없다는 거야
That says you don't need
music, concerts, friends.
넌 네가 무엇이 필요한지
알고 있어, 마이클
You know what you need, Michael.
어, 아닌데!
Uh, no!
나 나 나 나말야, 마이클
Me, me, me: M E Michael!
그래, 그렇구나
Yeah, I guess!
그런 말은 부끄럽나봐, 자기~
You're just too shy
to say that, Lover.
그래서 언제 보이스카웃 했는데?
So, when were you a boy scout?
♪ 'Hello it's me'
by Todd Rundgren ♪
정말 멋진 밤이다!
What a great night!
널 위해서 그런 반항을
할 수 있었던 것도 놀라워
It's amazing what one act of civil
disobedience can do for you.
온 세상이 내가 차를 몰고
와주기를 바라는 것 같아
I mean there's a whole world
that's waiting to be driven to
캐나다에도 갈 수 있을 거야
We could go to Canada!
이제 새 배터리도 있는데
왜 못 가겠어?
We got a new battery,
what's stopping us?
캐나다는 9시 30분이면 문 닫아
You know, I think
Canada closes at nine-thirty.
네가 하라고 하지 않았다면
난 결코 못했을 거야
You know, I never would've done this
if you hadn't talked me into it.
난 너한테 뭘 하라고 한 적 없어
I didn't talk you into anything.
아, 이제 그만 자야겠다
Well, I'm gonna call it a day.
- 잘 자
- Good night.
- 'Night!
그런데, 태워줘서 고마워
By the way, thanks for the ride.
이건 어떤 의미인데?
What was that for?
그냥 어떤 건지 알고 싶어서
I just wanted to see
what it was like.
어땠는데?
What was it like?
너도 했잖아!
You were there!
나...난 준비가 안 돼 있었어
I...I wasn't ready for it!
준비됐으면 어떻게 했을건데?
What would you've done differently?
모르지만, 입술로 어떻게 했겠지
I don't know,
something with my lips.
재밌겠는데
다음 번에 해보자
Sounds good.
Let's try that next time.
다음 번이 정확히 언젠데?
When exactly is next time?
잘 자
Good night.
그러고 가버리는데
잠이 잘도 오겠다
Yeah, I'm really gonna sleep after that!
번역수정: 김현정(fuchs@nate)
최종수정: 김은경(toy69@nate)
♪ 그대가 자유로워지는 게
내게 중요해요 ♪
♪ It's important to me~
that you got to have free~ ah~ ♪
♪ 그대가 나 때문에 변하는 건
원치 않으니까요~ ♪
♪ 'Cause I never want to make
you change for me~ ♪
애들아, 우리 너무 잘 한다
Boy, we're good. Haha.
그래, 진짜 잘 한다
Yeah, really good.
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24
자유배포 / 수정금지
네이트 드라마 24 자막팀
http://club.nate.com/24